

Sean Kipinä

- □ paintballsean@gmail.com

 □ +358451636995
- - 🕻 https://seankipina.com 🛛 🤨 Haapasaarentie 11 E 350, Helsinki, 00960

PROFILE

With a burning passion for learning and a drive to succeed, I am currently a dedicated student at Laurea University of Applied Sciences, Leppävaara Campus, Espoo, Finland, pursuing a BBA in Business Information Technology with a specialization in Cyber Security. My unique combination of theoretical expertise and practical experience sets me apart. I am thrilled to make a valuable contribution to the ever-evolving field of Information Technology. Along my professional journey, I had the privilege of leading the Customer Success Team (Offline) Group at Slush, where I flawlessly orchestrated event operations and delivered exceptional service to a staggering 13,000 attendees.

EDUCATION		
08.2023 – present	BBA Business Information Technology, Cyber Security, Laurea University of Applied Sciences (Leppävaara Campus)	Espoo, Finland
2018 – 2020	 AS Cybersecurity and Networking, Tacoma Community College Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society Member 4.0 out of 4.0 GPA High Honors 	Tacoma, United States
2010 – 2017	BA Digital Cinema & Minor Game Production, DePaul University	Chicago, United States

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

09.2023 - 12.2023

Slush, Customer Success Team (Offline) Group Lead

- Helsinki, Finland
- Recruiting, coaching and leading a group of Volunteers
- Overseeing and handling event info operations before and during the event
- Overseeing and organizing team members shifts and communications
- Providing service and information for 13 000 attendees before and during the event
- Helping customers inside and outside the venue
- Top-notch customer service!

11.2022 - 05.2023

McDonald's, Food Service Worker

Oulu, Finland

- Preparing ingredients and making food items according to recipes and guidelines
- Cleaning and maintaining equipment such as stoves, microwaves, blenders, grills, fryers, broilers, blenders, mixers, and other kitchen equipment
- Preparing food in accordance with health department regulations regarding preparation methods and storage conditions to ensure that food is safe to eat
- Preparing orders for pickup by customers or delivery by waitstaff to customers' tables

03.2022 - 08.2022

Walmart, Cashier

Puyallup,

United States

- Provides a positive customer experience with fair, friendly, and courteous service.
- Registers sales on a cash register by scanning items, itemizing and totaling customers' purchases.
- Resolves customer issues and answers questions.
- Maintains a safe and clean working environment by complying with procedures, rules, and regulations.

01.2020 - 01.2021

FedEx Ground, Package Handler

Fife, United States

- Load and unload packages from delivery vehicles for about 4 to 6 hours a day.
- Ensuring safety while performing various duties and ensuring a clean work area.
- Carry out work in accordance with company policies and guidelines.

07.2016 - 05.2017

Flexasoft, Videogame Tester

Redmond, United States

- Follow, complete, and update assigned test cases.
- Detect, research, and document software defects in a bugtracking system.
- Review product documentation, and report any errors as required.
- Sweeping game builds for bugs and software errors.
- Perform ad-hoc testing procedures to find bugs and gameplay issues.

CERTIFICATES

HTML5.0x: HTML5 and CSS Fundamentals ∂ | Microsoft Office Specialist: Word (Office 2016) ∂

Microsoft Office Specialist: PowerPoint (Office 2016) | Hygieniapassi

S INTERESTS

Photography | Indoor Climbing | Video Games

LANGUAGES

English (Native) | Spanish (B1) | Swedish (A1) | Suomi (A1)

SKILLS

Computer Skills

Customer Service Skills —

Food Industry Classifications: Food

Service